<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fontpage on fearness.org</title>
    <link>https://fearness.org/tags/fontpage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fontpage on fearness.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2016 21:33:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fearness.org/tags/fontpage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Freedom Is Not Free. Terrorists are trying to take it away!</title>
      <link>https://fearness.org/articles/freedom-isnt-free-terrorists/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2016 21:33:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fearness.org/articles/freedom-isnt-free-terrorists/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;freedom-isn-t-free&#34;&gt;Freedom Isn&amp;rsquo;t Free&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than any time in history terrorists have been working to take away our freedoms. Every day our rights are being encroached upon by those who would hurt their fellow man. We should be concerned with making sure we do our duty as it directly affects our honor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;without-honor-there-is-nothing&#34;&gt;Without honor there is nothing.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a few meaningful quotes to inspire you to honor your duty and secure yourself as a dutiful person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;Jesus said to them, &amp;ldquo;A prophet is not without honor except in his own town, among his relatives and in his own home.&amp;rdquo; ~ &lt;a href=&#34;http://biblehub.com/mark/6-4.htm&#34;&gt;Mark 6:4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;17&lt;/sup&gt;Honour all men. Love the brotherhood. Fear God. Honour the king. ~ &lt;a href=&#34;http://biblehub.com/1_peter/2-17.htm&#34;&gt;1 Peter 2:17&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And for some non biblical quotes&amp;hellip; Remember there is little we retain when we die besides our honor. Allah will judge us based on the honorable actions we performed while in this world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Who sows virtue reaps honor&amp;rdquo; ~ &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.brainyquote.com/quotes/quotes/l/leonardoda124544.html&#34;&gt;Leonardo da Vinci&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Hair on Men is an Abomination!</title>
      <link>https://fearness.org/articles/long-hair-abomination/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 19:29:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fearness.org/articles/long-hair-abomination/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is common these days that portrayals the portrayals of Jesus show him to have long hair. It is common practice in modern art to depict Jesus as having long hair. Jesus was also black, but that isn&amp;rsquo;t the point of this article. The bible doesn&amp;rsquo;t have much to say about this topic but luckily what it does have to say is very definitive. There is one place in the bible where Paul tells us that long hair on men is bad. King James Version this time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;14&lt;/sup&gt;Doth not even nature itself teach you, that, if a man have long hair, it is a shame unto him? &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=1+Corinthians+11%3A14&amp;amp;version=KJV&#34;&gt;1 Corinthians 11:14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that makes it very clear. It is a shame for men to have long hair. If you know of more bible testimony about this topic then feel free to email me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When We Die We are Reborn into Perfect Bodies.</title>
      <link>https://fearness.org/articles/reborn-in-perfect-bodies-free-from-defects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 23:52:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fearness.org/articles/reborn-in-perfect-bodies-free-from-defects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let us take a look at the chapter of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=2+Corinthians+5&amp;amp;version=NIV&#34;&gt;2 Corinthians 5&lt;/a&gt;. We will be using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.biblegateway.com/versions/New-International-Version-NIV-Bible/&#34;&gt;New International Version&lt;/a&gt; for this lesson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Lord has for us inscribed on stone our perfect genetic structure, untouched by sin and virus. We are forever flawed by those of us who have committed sin. Sin creates all the hate, pain and suffering in the world and is responsible for the defects in our DNA that cause cancer and many types of sickness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Let me take a moment to say that I hate it when people pick and choose verses without reading them in context. So we will read the whole chapter in tonight&amp;rsquo;s publication.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For we know that if the earthly tent we live in is destroyed, we have a building from God, an eternal house in heaven, not built by human hands. &lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt; Meanwhile we groan, longing to be clothed instead with our heavenly dwelling, &lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt; because when we are clothed, we will not be found naked. &lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt; For while we are in this tent, we groan and are burdened, because we do not wish to be unclothed but to be clothed instead with our heavenly dwelling, so that what is mortal may be swallowed up by life. &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt; Now the one who has fashioned us for this very purpose is God, who has given us the Spirit as a deposit, guaranteeing what is to come. - &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=2+Corinthians+5%3A1-5&amp;amp;version=NIV&#34;&gt;2 Corinthians 5:1-5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clearly in this scripture the phrase &lt;em&gt;earthly tent&lt;/em&gt; refers to our initial existence on earth in our mortal body that has been corrupted by sin. It is also very important to note that the Lord will cloth you because nakedness is a sin. It is especially wrong to be naked inside your own house, especially a house that God built. Verse 5 tells us that God fashions us with whatever hardships and gains that we deserve to create the person that we are today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;6&lt;/sup&gt;Therefore we are always confident and know that as long as we are at home in the body we are away from the Lord. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=2+Corinthians+5%3A6&amp;amp;version=NIV&#34;&gt;2 Corinthians 5:6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as we remain in our mortal bodies on Earth we are separated from the Lord. We must remember that faith will guide our transition to our immortal bodies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;7&lt;/sup&gt;For we live by faith, not by sight. - &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=2+Corinthians+5%3A7&amp;amp;version=NIV&#34;&gt;2 Corinthians 5:7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Faith is more important than what your mortal eyes can see and your mortal senses can sense. You must remember that beyond all of our mortal senses lives our perfect spirit which is tainted by the sin of mankind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;8&lt;/sup&gt; We are confident, I say, and would prefer to be away from the body and at home with the Lord. &lt;sup&gt;9&lt;/sup&gt; So we make it our goal to please him, whether we are at home in the body or away from it. &lt;sup&gt;10&lt;/sup&gt; For we must all appear before the judgment seat of Christ, so that each of us may receive what is due us for the things done while in the body, whether good or bad. - &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=2+Corinthians+5%3A8-10&amp;amp;version=NIV&#34;&gt;2 Corinthians 5:8-10&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scripture tells us that being with the Lord is preferable to life here on earth in our imperfect bodies. But rest assured that if you live a good life and repent and get baptized you might make it to be beside the hand of our Lord.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jesus Has Always Supported The Old Testament</title>
      <link>https://fearness.org/articles/jesus-and-the-old-testament/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 18:14:45 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fearness.org/articles/jesus-and-the-old-testament/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placebo Spells</title>
      <link>https://fearness.org/spells/placebospell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 22:14:47 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fearness.org/spells/placebospell/</guid>
      <description>This is&amp;hellip;. some content. I haven&amp;rsquo;t written anything yet for this page but trust me, someday I will. Maybe. Possibly. Here is a gif to entertain you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guidence will Guide you through thick and thin.</title>
      <link>https://fearness.org/articles/faith-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 13:41:32 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fearness.org/articles/faith-evidence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Faith will guide your path. You do not need evidence or proof to fulfill your goals. Just pray and you will find that everything you need will be provided for you by Allah.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jihad as an Obligation</title>
      <link>https://fearness.org/articles/jan-thirteenth-predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 19:16:37 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fearness.org/articles/jan-thirteenth-predictions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It seems my predictions on Allahs arrival have been twarted by evil. I&amp;rsquo;m
 not sure why it didn&amp;rsquo;t happen but I assume there is some holy reason
 that is beyond me. In the meantime I will bring you meaningful quotes
 from the great Holy Quran.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not equal are those of the believers who sit (at home), except those who
    are disabled (by injury or are blind or lame, etc.), and those who
    strive hard and fight in the Cause of Allah with their wealth and their
    lives. Allah has preferred in grades those who strive hard and fight
    with their wealth and their lives above those who sit (at home). Unto
    each, Allah has promised good (Paradise), but Allah has preferred
    those who strive hard and fight, above those who sit (at home) by a
    huge reward - &lt;a href=&#34;http://quran.com/4/95-96&#34;&gt;Quran 4:95&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fighting is prescribed for you, and ye dislike it. But it is possible
    that ye dislike a thing which is good for you, and that ye love a thing
    which is bad for you. But Allah knoweth, and ye know not. -
    &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.usc.edu/org/cmje/religious-texts/quran/verses/002-qmt.php#002.216&#34;&gt;Quran 2:216&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good News</title>
      <link>https://fearness.org/articles/the-good-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 20:03:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fearness.org/articles/the-good-news/</guid>
      <description>He is so close I can almost sense it. Every time I feel a chill go down my back I know that its the waves of purity that are radiated by the genuine soul lord Cthulhu! It has been six years, six months and six days since his last return. My fingers ache as I struggle to type this to keep you up to date on the latest Cthulhu news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Good Deed</title>
      <link>https://fearness.org/articles/no-good-deed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 22:21:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fearness.org/articles/no-good-deed/</guid>
      <description>The reason no good deed goes unpunished is simple. God is evil. The reason for this is there is no god, there is only evil demons who have tricked the masses into thinking there is one, however I digress. I will explain to you the technical reasoning behind why this phenomon occurs.
As long as people pray they generally have happy lives and bad things never happen to them. However when they sin, the evil jehovah who is really satan, punishes you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jesus Deception</title>
      <link>https://fearness.org/articles/jesus-deception/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 18:00:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fearness.org/articles/jesus-deception/</guid>
      <description>Satan was forever known in the old testament as the accuser. These stories in the bible have a basis in truth, but are horribly perverted from reality. As anyone who paid attention in sunday school knows, that often the accuser appeared in a story or parable, as if to administer a test of loyalty to to their LORD.
There are two distinct entities that we must define to prevent confusion further on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>