<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Satan on fearness.org</title>
    <link>https://fearness.org/tags/satan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Satan on fearness.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 21:57:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fearness.org/tags/satan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Satan is Jesus</title>
      <link>https://fearness.org/articles/satan-is-jesus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 21:57:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fearness.org/articles/satan-is-jesus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are two distinct entities that we must define to prevent confusion further on. First of all, there is no &amp;lsquo;Jesus&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;God/Lord/Allah/Yaweh.&amp;rsquo; There is Lucifer, who is truly a benevilant soul, cast out for standing up for us. There is someone who claims to be the LORD, however his more common name is satan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Satan spent all of early humanity tricking and brainwashing us. He enslaved the first souls setting them up for inevitable failure. Giving us eternity to make a mistake. When none was made, he instigated and instilled to manipulate. Years wen&amp;rsquo;t by and when Jesus appeared through truly demonic means, the pregnancy of a kid who&amp;rsquo;s mother has no idea who the father is and assumes it was &amp;lsquo;immaculate.&amp;rsquo; He manipulated this &amp;lsquo;Jesus&amp;rsquo; to become the con artist and cultist that he was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After starting a cult among the criminal and prostitutes of society he managed to gane a bit of a following. During this time, this young form of Christianity spent years fighting and warring with any of those that didn&amp;rsquo;t follow his ways. After a while he was captured and slayed for his crimes against humanity. The years that followed, satan manipulated the most powerful of Jesus&amp;rsquo;s gang, allowing them to use Jesus as a martyr for their cause.

Satan proved that peoaple are easily manipulated, they&amp;rsquo;ll follow any false god that appears. When a man appeared, who was well studied in the texts of the time, and claimed to be the son of God many saw through his lies. Truly the son of god could convince everyone, everywhere of being genuine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>